[upbeat music]
（欢快的音乐）
- Uh, hey, guys, I got our sleeping bags.
呃，嘿，伙计们，我拿了我们的睡袋。
Little help?
来点帮助？
- Yes!
好！
Oh, you're done, perfect.
哦，你完成了，太好了。
Now we can practice for our sleepover at the history museum.
现在我们可以练习在历史博物馆的睡衣派对了。
- Practice sleeping?
练习睡觉？
I can do that with my eyes closed.
我可以闭着眼睛做。
- No, practice not sleeping.
不，练习不睡觉。
This is finally our year to go on the big class trip,
这终于是我们去大型班级旅行的那一年，
and something epic always happens,
而且总会有一些史诗般的事情发生，
and if it happens in the middle of the night,
如果它发生在午夜时分，
I want to be awake so I can say,
我希望我能醒着，这样我就可以说，
"I was there when..."
“我当时在场...”
- When what? - It's a saying.
- 在场什么？ - 这是一句俗语。
- That says what? - That says we saw the epic moment that became the stuff of legend.
- 那说的是什么？ - 那说的是我们见证了成为传奇的史诗时刻。
- When?
- 什么时候？
- It hasn't happened yet. - Then how did we see it?
- 还没发生。 - 那我们怎么看到的？
- We didn't, but we're hoping to be there
- 我们没看到，但我们希望能亲历
when it happens. - When what happens?
它发生的那一刻。 - 什么发生的那一刻？
together: The epic moment!
一起：史诗般的时刻！
- Like the year Nate Powell got his pajamas stuck
就像那年内特·鲍威尔的睡衣被
on the saber tooth tiger--
剑齿虎卡住——
oh, and pantsed himself in front of everyone.
哦，还在大家面前露出了内裤。
- Hey, I wonder what's gonna happen this year.
嘿，我想知道今年会发生什么。
- Oscar's always sticking his head in stuff.
奥斯卡总是把头伸进各种东西里。
Maybe he'll get it stuck in something at the museum.
也许他会在博物馆里把头卡在什么东西里。
- Now why would you go and stick your head in that?
那你为什么要往那里面伸头呢？
- I just wanted to see if it would fit.
我只是想看看它能不能装下我的头。
[all laugh]
[大家都笑了]
- That would be epic,
那样会很壮观，
but nobody really gets their head caught in stuff.
但没人真的会把头卡在东西里。
- Uh, guys?
呃，伙计们？
Dicky.
迪基。
- I just wanted to see if it would fit.
我只是想看看它会不会合适。
- Turn your head the other way.
把头转向另一边。
- Whoa.
哇。
- Well, time to not get to sleep.
好吧，看来今晚睡不成了。
- Dawn, we're just as excited as you are,
Dawn，我们和你一样兴奋，
but don't you think it's better to get as much rest as possible
但你不觉得尽可能多休息会更好吗
before we go? - He has a point.
在我们出发前？ - 他说得有道理。
Shouldn't you be doing the exact opposite of what your plan is?
你不应该完全按照你的计划相反的来做吗？
- Even I see the value in a good night's sleep.
- 就连我也明白好好睡一觉的价值。
- You play like you train,
- 你比赛的方式应该像你训练时一样，
and you don't train for a marathon
- 而你不会通过坐在椅子上来为马拉松训练。 - 我会。
by sitting in a chair. - I would.
- 听起来很聪明。 - 我现在就在训练。
- Sounds smart. - I'm training right now.
- 好吧，别熬夜，
- Fine, don't stay up,
- 但如果这个历史性的时刻发生时你们都在睡觉，
but if this epic moment happens while you guys are all asleep,
- 我可不会叫醒你们。
I'm not waking you.
- 好吧，我们会整夜不睡。这能有多难？
- All right, we'll stay up all night.
好的，我们整晚都不睡。
How hard could it be?
这能有多难？
[both snoring]
[两人打呼噜]
- [grumbles]
- [咕哝]
- It's only been five minutes, you wimps.
- 才过了五分钟，你们这些懦夫。
[upbeat music]
[轻快的音乐]
Well, well, well,
哎呀，哎呀，哎呀，
looks like I was the only one to stay up last night.
看来昨晚只有我一个人熬夜了。
[sneezes] - Bless you.
[打喷嚏] - 保佑你。
[boys chuckle]
[男孩们轻笑]
- What's so funny?
- 有什么好笑的？
- Just that you stayed up all night
- 只是因为你整晚没睡
and got yourself sick. - And if you're sick,
还把自己弄病了。- 如果你生病了，
there's no way Mom and Dad
爸妈肯定不会
will let you go on the trip.
让你去旅行的。
- Oh, please. I probably just caught a whiff
- 哦，拜托。我可能只是闻到了
of your body spray.
你的香水味。
- [sniffs]
- [嗅]
[groans] He is not wearing body spray.
[呻吟] 他没喷香水。
- Well, one sneeze doesn't mean I'm sick.
- 好吧，打一个喷嚏不代表我生病了。
[sneezing] - Bless you.
[打喷嚏声] - 保佑你。
Bless you... Bless you.
保佑你... 保佑你。
- Bless you. - [sneezes]
- 保佑你。 - [打喷嚏声]
- Bless you.
- 保佑你。
- Uh-oh. [boys laugh]
- 哎呀。 [男孩们笑]
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪
- What're you doing?
- 你在做什么？
- Sweating out the germs.
- 在排出细菌。
- I think you're just making 'em angry.
- 我觉得你只是在激怒它们。
- There. I feel better already.
- 好了，我已经感觉好多了。
Also, I feel... really dizzy.
而且，我感觉...真的很晕。
- Well, look on the bright side, at least we get to go to the museum.
- 好吧，往好处想，至少我们可以去博物馆了。
We'll tell you all about it.
我们会告诉你所有关于它的事情。
[panting] Okay,
[喘气] 好吧，
if I can't kick it, I'm gonna hide it.
如果我不能摆脱它，我就把它藏起来。
Look, I am not missing that epic moment.
看，我不能错过那个史诗般的时刻。
Ricky, you have to help me hide this from Mom and Dad.
瑞奇，你得帮我瞒着爸爸妈妈。
- Why me? - Well, we all know you've been faking well for years
- 为什么是我？ - 嗯，我们都知道你多年来装病装得很像
so you never have to miss a day at school.
所以你从来不会错过一天的学校。
- Well, it is true that my attendance is perfect.
嗯，我的出勤率确实是完美的。
Whoo-whoo!
呼呼！
But I'm sorry, I've worked too long
但很抱歉，我花了太多时间和精力
and too hard mastering my "faking well" techniques
来精进我的“伪装得好”的技巧
to share them with you.
不想与你分享。
- Well, then I'm sorry
那好吧，我也很抱歉
because you're gonna have to miss the trip too.
因为你也将错过这次旅行。
- What do you mean? I'm going.
你什么意思？我要去的。
- Not if you're sick. - But I'm not sick.
如果你生病了就不能去。但我没生病。
- Yet.
现在还没有。
I feel a very wet sneeze coming with your name on it.
我感觉一个非常湿润的喷嚏即将以你的名字为名。
- Make it as wet as you want. It won't matter.
你想让它多湿就多湿，无所谓。
I know how to fake being well.
我知道怎么装作没事。
- [sighs] Fine.
好吧。
I really didn't want to have to do this, but...
我真的不想这么做，但是……
I'm playing my Quad Card.
我要打出我的四重王牌。
[all gasp]
（众人惊呼）
- Yeah, that's right, and as we all know,
没错，我们都知道，
when one of us plays their card,
当我们中的一个人打出王牌时，
the other three have to do what we say,
其他三个人必须按照我们的要求去做，
no questions asked.
无条件服从。
- You had your Quad Card in your pajamas?
- 你把你的四重卡放在睡衣里了？
- No questions asked!
- 无条件服从！
- Dawn, you only get one Quad Card a year.
- 晨曦，你一年只能有一张四重卡。
Are you sure this is what you want to use it for?
你确定要用在这件事上吗？
- Question!
- 提问！
- Fine, then let the record show
- 好吧，那么让记录显示
that one Dawn Abigail Harper
一位名叫晨曦·阿比盖尔·哈珀的人
has played her Quad Card for the year
已经在今年上午8点35分使用了她的四重卡
at 8:35 a.m. on this,
在这个月的第五天。
the fifth day of the month.
这个月的第五天。
Nicky, did you get that?
尼基，你记下了吗？
- It is gotten.
- 已经记下了。
- You had all that in your pajamas?
- 你把所有东西都放在睡衣里了？
- No questions asked.
- 不问任何问题。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- [grunts] - [sneezes]
- [咕哝声] - [打喷嚏声]
- Oh, bless you.
- 哦，保佑你。
- How's it coming with the drink?
- 饮料准备得怎么样了？
- Welcome to Ricky's Faking Well Seminar.
- 欢迎来到瑞奇的假装良好研讨会。
Step one:
第一步：
Drink...
喝...
that.
那个。
- [groaning] Ugh, what does that do?
呃，那有什么作用？
- Makes us laugh.
让我们笑。
[boys laugh]
（男孩们笑）
- Now, real Step One... - [groans]
现在，真正的第一步...
- You need to master the art of hiding your symptoms.
你需要掌握隐藏症状的艺术。
If you cough, turn it into a laugh.
如果你咳嗽，把它变成笑声。
Like this... [coughs]
像这样...（咳嗽）
[laughs]
[笑]
Step Two:
第二步：
If you sound stuffed up,
如果你听起来鼻塞，
just pretend you smell something bad
就假装闻到了什么难闻的东西
and blame it on Dicky.
然后怪到迪基头上。
- Oh, if it helps, I can arrange it so you don't have to pretend.
- 哦，如果这有帮助，我可以安排让你不必假装。
- Yeah, that's all right. Thanks.
- 是的，那很好。谢谢。
- Now, Step Three: What you nee--
- 现在，第三步：你需要——
[all groan] Aw, Dicky.
[大家呻吟] 啊，迪基。
- What? Just trying to help.
- 什么？只是想帮忙。
- Ugh, dude.
- 呃，伙计。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Oh, hey, Mae's mom should be here any minute to pick us up.
- 哦，梅的妈妈应该随时会来接我们。
- Okay, but you still have to get past the final step:
- 好的，但你还得过最后一关：
Mom's good-bye hug.
妈妈的告别拥抱。
The trick is, don't let her get in too tight.
诀窍是，别让她抱得太紧。
- Yeah. Aw, here comes the hugger.
- 是啊。哦，拥抱者来了。
- Aww, my little babies are going
- 哦，我的小宝贝们要去
on their big overnight trip.
他们的大冒险之旅了。
- Looks like she's bringing her A-game.
- 看来她要全力以赴了。
- Yeah. - Come here.
是啊。来这里。
Come on. Come on.
来吧。来吧。
Come on--hey, Dawn... [grunts]
来吧——嘿，Dawn……[咕哝]
Okay, this is not a hug. Come here.
好吧，这不是拥抱。过来。
This is a hug.
这才是拥抱。
Mm.
嗯。
Oh, you feel warm.
哦，你感觉很温暖。
You're not getting sick, are you?
你不会是生病了吧？
- No.
没有。
- You sound a little congested.
你听起来有点鼻塞。
- I'm fine. Ugh, Dicky.
- 我没事。呃，迪基。
- Okay, you know, there is a nasty bug going around.
- 好吧，你知道，最近有个讨厌的病毒在传播。
I better take your temperature.
我最好给你量量体温。
Here. - [mumbles]
给。- [咕哝]
- You had that in your pocket?
- 你把它放在口袋里了？
- Yeah, that's why it's called
- 是啊，所以它才叫做
a ther-mom-eter. [chuckles]
体温计。[轻笑]
- Uh, Mom, you better double check Dicky's overnight bag.
- 呃，妈妈，你最好检查一下迪基的过夜包。
He could have forgotten his underwear.
他可能忘了带内裤。
- Or he could have packed only underwear.
- 或者他可能只带了内裤。
- You never know which way this guy's gonna go.
你永远不知道这家伙会怎么想。
- You're right.
你说得对。
- What do we do?
我们该怎么办？
- Put that in your mouth. - No, I'm not getting sick.
把它放进嘴里。
- I'm not getting sick either.
不，我不会生病的。
[grunts]
我也不会生病的。
[dog whimpers]
（咕哝声）
- Hmm, Dicky's actually got
（狗呜咽声）
a pretty good underwear to clothes ration.
嗯，Dicky的内衣和衣服的比例其实挺不错的。
[thermometer beeps]
（体温计哔哔声）
- [mouthing] - Epic moment.
- [mouthing] - 史诗时刻。
- Okay, let's take a look.
- 好的，让我们看看。
[clears throat]
Ah, normal... [chuckles]
啊，正常... [chuckles]
But you do have a touch of puppy breath.
但你确实有一点小狗的气息。
[upbeat music]
- ♪ La la la la la ♪ ♪ La la la la la la ♪
- ♪ 啦啦啦啦啦 ♪ ♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
- This is it, guys. [sniffles]
- 就是现在，伙计们。 [sniffles]
[sighs] We've been dreaming
[sighs] 我们从一年级开始
about this trip since first grade.
就梦想着这次旅行。
- Hey, Harpers,
嘿，哈珀家的人，
there's a contest to guess who the epic moment
有个比赛猜谁会是那个精彩时刻的主角。你们想参加吗？
is gonna happen to. You want in?
当然想参加。
- Uh, of course we want in.
每个人都在拿出他们最好的零食。
- Everybody's putting in their best snacks.
赢家通吃。
Winner takes all.
我参加，而且我会赢走所有。
- I'm in, and I will be taking all.
哦，嘿，你们选了谁？
- Oh, hey, who'd you guys pick? - Oscar.
奥斯卡。
There's a lot of places he could stick his head.
他有很多地方可以把头伸进去。
- I went with Mae and Molly.
我选了梅和莫莉。
They've been having some drama lately.
他们最近有些戏剧性的事情。
It's been really bad.
情况真的很糟糕。
I can't wait!
我等不及了！
- All right, everyone, here comes our tour guide,
好了，各位，我们的导游来了，
so get with your buddies.
快和你的伙伴们站在一起。
- Hey, everyone, I'm Pamela, and I'd like to welcome you
大家好，我是Pamela，欢迎大家
to the history museum.
来到历史博物馆。
You know, I took this same trip when I was your age.
你们知道吗，我在你们这个年纪也参加了同样的旅行。
[chuckles] And now I work here.
[轻笑] 而现在我在这里工作。
- [singsong] Epic moment here we come.
[唱歌般] 史诗般的时刻即将到来。
- Nothing can stop us now.
- 现在没有什么能阻止我们了。
- [sneezes] - Bless you.
- （打喷嚏声）- 保佑你。
- Who was that? - No more "Bless yous."
- 那是谁？ - 不要再“保佑你”了。
If any of you are sick, fess up now
如果你们中有谁生病了，现在就坦白
so your parents can come get you.
这样你们的父母可以来接你们。
There's a nasty bug that's going around,
有一种讨厌的病毒正在传播，
and my Gram-Gram's 90th birthday is coming up,
而我奶奶的90岁生日即将到来，
and I will not miss it.
我绝不会错过。
She's having a petting zoo.
她要办一个宠物动物园。
[sniffing]
（嗅鼻子声）
I smell puppy breath.
我闻到了小狗的呼吸。
- [sniffles]
- Well, well, well,
哎呀，哎呀，哎呀，
guess who's "snot" staying here.
猜猜谁不会留在这里了。
You...gone.
你...走了。
- That was close.
好险。
- How am I gonna hide how sick I am from him?
我该怎么瞒住他我病得有多重？
[sneezes]
（打喷嚏）
And everyone else?
还有其他人呢？
- Sorry, Dawn, we helped you get here, but...
对不起，Dawn，我们帮你来到这里，但是...
you're on your own now.
你现在得靠自己了。
- At least we're not gonna miss the epic moment.
至少我们不会错过这史诗般的时刻。
- [sneezes]
（打喷嚏）
- [coughs] - [sniffles]
（咳嗽）（抽鼻子）
- Well, looks like I'm not on my own anymore.
看来我不再是一个人了。
[laughs]
（笑）
[coughs]
（咳嗽）
[laughs]
（笑）
Jokes.
开玩笑的。
[sighs]
（叹气）
[upbeat music]
[all coughing]
大家都在咳嗽
- Ow.
哎哟。
- Great, now you got us sick. What're we gonna do?
太好了，你让我们都生病了。我们该怎么办？
- Ugh, my nose hole is running.
呃，我的鼻孔在流鼻涕。
together: Mine too.
我也是。
- This is hopeless. Now that we're all sick,
这真是无望了。现在我们都生病了，
there's no way we'll ever be able to hide it
我们永远也瞒不过塔里安校长了。我是说，看看他。
from Principal Tarian. I mean, look at him.
哈！
- Ha! [snaps and claps]
啪啪！
What do we have here?
这里有什么？
An orange, huh, Natlee?
一个橙子，嗯，Natlee？
Need a little extra vitamin C for something?
需要额外的维生素C吗？
Like, perhaps... a cold?
比如，也许... 感冒？
- No, I'm just really into citrus right now.
- 不，我只是现在特别喜欢柑橘类水果。
- See, I can't take this pressure.
- 看，我受不了这种压力。
We should just tell him the truth.
我们应该告诉他真相。
- No, I didn't play my Quad Card just to get "gone'd."
- 不，我打出我的Quad卡不是为了被“消失”。
- Ah, great, now my other nose hole is running.
- 啊，糟了，我另一边的鼻孔也开始流鼻涕了。
[sniffles]
[吸鼻涕声]
- Dawn's right. We're not gonna let
黎明说得对。我们不会让
a little sniffling, sneezing, coughing, body aches,
一点点抽鼻子、打喷嚏、咳嗽、身体酸痛、
chills, fever, nausea, stuffy head--
发冷、发烧、恶心、鼻塞——
[coughing and hacking]
[咳嗽和喘息]
[gulps]
[吞咽]
[gasps] And whatever that was...
[喘气] 还有刚才那是什么...
keep us from seeing the epic moment.
阻止我们见证这一历史时刻。
- Which is about to happen. It's showtime.
- 马上就要发生了。表演时间到。
- Ugh, seriously? - What?
- 呃，真的吗？
- First, you started wearing sparkle bracelets,
- 起初，你开始戴闪亮手链，
like I do,
就像我一样，
then it was bedazzled barrettes,
然后是镶钻的发夹，
like I do,
就像我一样，
and now you're wearing cat shirts?
现在你穿上了猫图案的衬衫？
Huh, I wonder where you got that idea?
嗯，我想知道你从哪里得到这个想法的？
Oh, right...
哦，对了...
me! all: Ooh!
我！
- Reow.
喵。
- Everybody knows cat shirts are my thing, Molly.
大家都知道猫图案的衬衫是我的风格，莫莉。
- You can't be the only one in the world
你不能成为世界上唯一一个穿猫图案衬衫的人，梅。
who gets to wear cat shirts, Mae.
世界上不能只有我一个人穿猫衬衫，Mae。
all: Ooh!
哦！
- Oh, my gosh.
哦，天哪。
Your shirt says, "You've gotta be 'kitten' me."
你的衬衫上写着，“你得‘小猫’我。”
- Aww, and yours says, "Leave 'meow-t' of it."
哎呀，你的上面写着，“别‘猫’我。”
I love it. - I love yours.
我喜欢。
- Cat shirt twins forever?
我喜欢你的。
both: Aww.
猫衬衫双胞胎永远？
all: Aww.
哎呀。
- Aww, I used to have friends.
哎呀，我以前有朋友的。
Speaking of things that don't exist anymore,
说到不复存在的东西，
let's go check out the mastodon.
我们去看看乳齿象吧。
- Is it too late to change my pick
- 现在改选导游还来得及吗？
to the tour guide?
- 最后一次告诉你，Oscar，
- For the last time, Oscar,
博物馆里天黑后什么都不会活过来。
nothing comes to life in the museum after dark.
- 你看起来不太好。
- You don't look so good. - I get it.
- 我明白了，
You don't like sweater-vests.
你不喜欢毛背心。
- No, dude, your face. It's, like, gray and wet.
- 不，伙计，是你的脸，看起来灰灰的，湿漉漉的。
- Well, yours is taupe and pasty.
- 好吧，你的脸是灰褐色的，苍白的。
- Would you listen to yourselves?
- 你们听听自己在说什么？
- Can't. My left ear is ringing.
- 听不见。我左耳在响。
- Okay, enough.
- 好了，够了。
Do I feel and look terrible? Yes.
我是不是感觉和看起来都很糟糕？是的。
- Horrible. - Worse than ever.
- 糟透了。 - 比以往任何时候都糟。
- Goblin. - Hey.
- 小妖精。 - 嘿。
- But do you see me complaining? No, and why?
- 但你们看我有抱怨吗？没有，为什么？
- Because you don't have to look at you. - Okay, everybody, stop answering me.
- 因为你不用看你自己。 - 好了，大家，别回答我了。
- There's a BOGO on snow globes.
- 雪景球买一送一。
- She's gonna hit the rare vases.
- 她要撞到那些稀有花瓶了。
The epic moment we've all been waiting for is about to go down.
我们期待已久的史诗时刻即将上演。
- Vitamin C, pump the breaks!
- 维生素C，刹车！
[boots scratching]
[靴子刮擦声]
all: Aww.
大家：哎呀。
- Really?
- 真的吗？
- This epic moment better happen soon.
- 这个史诗般的时刻最好快点发生。
Before... - [sneezes]
在...之前 - [打喷嚏]
- That. - [sneezes]
- 那个。 - [打喷嚏]
- And that.
- 还有那个。
[sneezes]
[打喷嚏]
[groaning] And that.
[呻吟] 还有那个。
- No, no, wait-- [sputters]
- 不，不，等等-- [咳嗽]
- Oh, no, here comes Principal Tarian.
- 哦，不，Tarian校长来了。
- All right, who's the sneezer?
- 好吧，谁在打喷嚏？
- I didn't hear anything. - I'm pretty sure it's
- 我什么都没听到。 - 我很确定是
the guy covered in tissues.
那个满身纸巾的家伙。
- I distinctly heard three sneezes.
- 我清楚地听到了三次打喷嚏。
"Achoo, achoo, achoo."
“啊嚏，啊嚏，啊嚏。”
- Oh, that.
- 哦，那个。
That was just us making train sounds.
那只是我们在模仿火车声。
- Yes, all aboard the Museum Fun Train.
是的，全体登上博物馆趣味列车。
together: Choo choo choo!
一起：嘟嘟嘟！
- Well, I appreciate your enthusiasm
嗯，我很欣赏你们对博物馆和铁路旅行的热情。
for both museums and rail travel.
继续吧。
Carry on.
好了，各位，那太危险了。
- Okay, guys, that was too close.
我们不能冒险被...[阿嚏]
We can't risk getting-- [sneezes]
一起：嘟嘟！- [阿嚏]
together: Choo choo! - [sneezes]
一起：嘟嘟！
together: Choo choo!
- 呜呜！
- Whoo-whoo!
[阿嚏] 一起：嘟嘟！
- [sneezes] together: Choo choo!
- [sneezes] together: Choo choo.
- We can sneeze in there. - Yeah.
- 我们可以在那里打喷嚏。 - 是的。
- [sneezes] - Choo...
both: Choo. [sneezes]
together: Choo choo.
- Well, this place looks soundproof.
- 嗯，这个地方看起来隔音。
Guess we can sneeze all we want.
猜我们可以尽情打喷嚏了。
[all sneezing]
[大家都在打喷嚏]
- All right, is everyone done?
- 好了，大家都打完了吗？
- I am. - Me too.
- 我打完了。 - 我也是。
- I'm empty. - All right.
- 我打完了。 - 好的。
Let's go catch up with the group.
我们去找大部队吧。
- Wait, where'd the door go? - It was right here.
- 等等，门去哪儿了？ - 它刚才就在这儿。
- There's gonna be a doorknob here somewhere.
- 门把手应该就在这附近。
- There better be. Otherwise we're trapped in here.
- 最好有，不然我们就困在这里了。
- Okay, hold on.
- 好的，稍等。
I'll just call Mae to come let us out.
我给梅打电话让她来开门。
If I had any signal. - Of course, there's no signal.
如果我有信号的话。
We're in caveman times.
当然，没有信号。
- All right, everyone, stand back.
我们简直回到了石器时代。
I got this.
好了，大家，往后站。
Ah...
我能搞定。
Whoa. Those are real rocks.
啊...
- I can't believe this.
哇。那些是真的石头。
After all we've done to get here,
我真不敢相信。
now we're going to miss the epic moment.
我们费尽周折来到这里，
- [sighs] Well, none of this would have
现在却要错过那个激动人心的时刻。
happened if we'd just admitted we were sick
如果我们一开始就承认我们生病了，
and let Principal Tarian "gone" us.
让Tarian校长把我们‘送走’就好了。
- No, none of this would have happened,
- 没错，这一切都不会发生，
if Dawn didn't get us all sick.
如果Dawn没有让我们都生病的话。
- Well, it's not my fault somebody shut the un-findable door.
- 好吧，有人关上了那扇找不到的门，这可不是我的错。
- Well, it's not my fault. - It's not my fault.
- 好吧，这不是我的错。 - 也不是我的错。
- Well, somebody needs to be blamed!
- 总之，得有人负责！
- Then I blame you! - And I blame you!
- 那我就怪你！ - 我也怪你！
- And I blame you. - And I blame all of you.
- 我也怪你。 - 我怪你们所有人。
[all grunting and shouting at once]
[所有人同时发出哼哼声和喊叫声]
[all breathing heavy] - [groans]
[所有人呼吸沉重] - [呻吟]
Me sick.
我生病了。
- Me sicker.
- 我病得更重。
- Me sickest.
- 我病得最重。
- Not...
- 不是...
a contest.
比赛。
[all shivering]
[所有人颤抖]
- So cold.
- 好冷。
- Fire... - Huh.
- 火... - 嗯。
- Fake.
- 假的。
- Here.
- 这里。
[all breathing heavy]
[所有人呼吸沉重]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- [sighs]
- [叹气]
- Uh-oh. Hide.
- 哎呀。躲起来。
- Too late. [grunts]
- 太晚了。[咕哝]
- Must stand upright.
- 必须站直。
[all grunting] Be...cavemen.
[所有人咕哝] 做...穴居人。
- There's Mae. She can help.
- 那里是Mae。她能帮忙。
I need to get her attention.
我需要引起她的注意。
- I got this. [grunts]
- 我能搞定。[咕哝]
- Did that cave boy just move?
- 那个洞穴男孩刚刚动了？
- Are you seeing things, Mae?
- 你是不是看错了，梅？
'Cause if you're getting sick, you're gone.
- 因为如果你生病了，你就得离开。
- [whispering] Help us, Mae.
- [低语] 帮帮我们，梅。
- Okay, now I'm pretty sure that cave-girl just said,
- 好吧，我现在几乎可以肯定那个洞穴女孩刚刚说了，
"Hep bus smay."
“Hep bus smay.”
- That's ridiculous.
- 这太荒谬了。
That just sounds like someone with a cold saying,
那听起来就像是一个感冒的人在说，
"Help us, Mae," and that wouldn't happen.
“帮帮我们，梅，” 但那是不可能发生的。
You know why?
你知道为什么吗？
'Cause they'd be gone.
因为他们会消失。
That's the Harper Quads.
那是哈珀家的四胞胎。
- I think he just said,
- 我想他刚说的是，
"Those look like genuine cave people."
- “那些看起来像是真正的穴居人。”
- Is it getting hot in here?
- 这里是不是变热了？
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
I don't feel so good.
我感觉不太好。
- Dawn doesn't look so good.
- 道恩看起来也不太好。
- I think I'm about to--
- 我想我快要——
- I think she's about to--
- 我觉得她快要——
- [gagging]
- [作呕声]
[vomiting] [all scream]
[呕吐] [所有人尖叫]
- [gagging] - No, no, no, please.
- [作呕声] - 不，不，不，请不要。
- [vomiting] [all scream]
- [呕吐] [所有人尖叫]
- [gagging]
- [作呕声]
[all scream] - Oh, my goodness.
[所有人尖叫] - 哦，天哪。
- Why do we keep looking? - I don't know.
- 我们为什么还一直看？ - 我不知道。
[all mouthing]
[所有人闭嘴]
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
- That's it!
- 就是这样！
[mouthing]
- [默念]
- If I understood him correctly...
- 如果我没理解错他的话...
you guys are in big trouble.
- 你们麻烦大了。
- Bye, guys. - Yeah, have fun without us.
- 再见，伙计们。 - 是啊，没有我们你们好好玩。
- Can't believe we're gonna miss this year's epic moment.
- 真不敢相信我们会错过今年的精彩时刻。
- What do you mean? You were the epic moment.
- 你什么意思？你们就是那个精彩时刻。
- We were?
- 我们是吗？
- Yeah. - Totally.
- 是的。 - 绝对是。
- Duh. - Of course.
- 当然。 - 当然了。
- I mean, you guys are the Hurling Harpers.
- 我是说，你们可是Hurling Harpers。
[boys fake vomit] [all laugh]
[男孩们假装呕吐] [大家都笑了]
- So, who had the Harper Quads in the contest?
- 那么，谁在比赛中押了Harper四胞胎？
- That would be me.
- 那是我。
- What? Mae, you had us? How could you?
- 什么？Mae，你押了我们？你怎么能这样？
- How could I not?
- 我怎么能不押呢？
I mean, I love you guys, but...
我是说，我爱你们，但是...
have you met you?
你们自己见过自己吗？
- She does have a point.
- 她确实有道理。
- Now everybody pay up.
- 现在大家都付钱吧。
Your best snacks, let's go.
你们最好的零食，来吧。
Hummus?
鹰嘴豆泥？
Really, Molly?
真的，莫莉？
- Guess we have to pay up, too.
看来我们也得付钱了。
- Uh-uh. I don't want your germs.
不不，我不要你的细菌。
I'd rather eat Molly's hummus. Ugh.
我宁愿吃莫莉的鹰嘴豆泥。呃。
- Well, at least we get to say...
至少我们可以说……
"We were there when." - When what?
“我们在那里见证了。” - 见证了什么？
- When we became the Hurling Harpers.
我们成为哈林哈珀斯的那一刻。
- The stuff of legend.
传奇般的存在。
[all coughing and hacking]
【所有人咳嗽和干咳】
- Okay, come on.
- 好了，来吧。
[dog sneezes]
【狗打喷嚏】
- I wonder how Squishy got sick.
- 我想知道Squishy是怎么生病的。
- ♪ Oh-oh oh-oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh oh-oh ♪
[whistling]
【吹口哨】
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪